serverhub.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Agreement - ServerHub User Agreement | ServerHub

Welcome to the ServerHub® networks Services website ("ServerHub®") operated by Eonix Corporation ("Eonix"). The Website products and services (collectively, the "Services") are offered by Eonix through Web pages and linked pages that display the ServerHub® Hosting Service navigation bar and include a footer link to the ServerHub® Hosting Services Privacy Agreement. By accessing the Website or using any of the Services, you agree to be bound by our User Agreement as well as our Privacy Agreement. Because the User Agreements contains legal obligations, please read them carefully. If you reside outside of the United States, you are contracting with Eonix Corporation Canada. If you have any questions, please refer to the Help section on the Site.

##### Section 1. Our Commitment to Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected by us and used. 

Eonix Corporation and ServerHub® reserves the right to make amendments to this agreement from time to time. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting on-line at this location. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. You may identify whether Eonix Corporation and ServerHub® has revised this Privacy Policy by noting the "Effective Date" above. Your continued use of the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

##### Section 2. The Way We Use Your Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers and third-party vendors. We would not disclose anything to third parties that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

##### Section 3 . Our Commitment to Account and Data Security.

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

##### Section 4. Personal and Business Information

When you order services through ServerHub®, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form to us to allow us to process your order, provide you with the services you order from us, and to provide ongoing technical support for your account. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, phone number, and address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

By purchasing our services, you agree to comply with our  False or missing contact information policy and provide and maintain accurate, complete and updated information. After you have ordered our services, we may be in communication with you about your account. These communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality services that are responsive to your needs. As a result, we may maintain information about our communications with you for future use.

##### Section 5. Disclosure of Personal and Business Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide service. 

In the event that this policy changes, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit the disclosure of your information to third parties for any purpose other than your ordering and ongoing use of our services. 

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personal Information to others. We do provide some of our services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners and other third parties. 

We and our service partners use your Personal Information to operate our sites and to deliver our services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased on this site or release your address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered. 

Occasionally, ServerHub® may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personal Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. 

We will disclose Personal Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use ServerHub® services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that ServerHub® in good faith believe to be unlawful. 

ServerHub® may also use the Personal Information collected to contact customers regarding important changes to our site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. 

You will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers through our client portal or by sending an email request at [legal@serverhub.com](mailto:legal@serverhub.com).

##### Section 6. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy  

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

##### Section 7. Access to your Personal Information

You always have access to the information we have about you. To review and update your personal contact information, simply log into our client portal.

##### Section 8. No Spam, Spyware of Spoofing

We and our users do not tolerate spam. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content, but we do not permanently store messages sent through these tools. If you send an email to an email address that is not registered in our community (via Refer-a-Friend or other tools), we do not permanently store that email or use that email address for any marketing purpose. We do not rent or sell these email addresses.

##### Section 9. Account Protection

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify ServerHub® and change your password.

##### Section 10. General

Eonix Corporation is located at 3155 East Patrick Lane, Las Vegas, NV 89120. If you reside outside of the United States and are registered on this site, the policies are administered by Eonix Corporation Canada, International Policy Department, located at: PO BOX 4798 Station Main, Vancouver British Columbia, V6B 4A4 Canada. 

If any provision of this Agreement is held to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be struck and the remaining provisions shall be enforced. In our sole discretion, we may assign this Agreement in accordance with the Notices Section. Headings are for reference purposes only and do not limit the scope or extent of such section. Our failure to act with respect to a breach by you or others does not waive our right to act with respect to subsequent or similar breaches. We do not guarantee we will take action against all breaches of this Agreement. 

We may amend this Agreement at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site. Except as stated elsewhere, all amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. Additionally, we will notify you through the Site's message center tools. This Agreement may not be otherwise amended except in a writing signed by you and us. This Agreement sets forth the entire understanding and agreement between us with respect to the subject matter hereof. 

****This User Agreement was last revised on June 13, 2012.
